lydiasuniforms.com 2008-12-17

# Scrubs Nursing Uniforms | Cheap Discount Nurse Scrubs

Privacy Policy  
Security Statement  
General Browsing  
Collection, Disclosure, and Usage of Personal Information  
List Removal Instructions  
Use of Cookies  
Links

**  
****PRIVACY POLICY** **  
** LydiasUniforms.com values its customers and respects their privacy. We collect customer information in an effort to improve your shopping experience and to communicate with you about our products, services, and promotions. LydiasUniforms.com recognizes that it must maintain and use customer information responsibly.   
**  
** Complying with the Children's Online Privacy Protection Act of 1998, 

we will never knowingly request personally identifiable information from anyone under the age of 13 without prior verifiable parental consent.  If we become aware that a subscriber is under the age of 13 and has signed up without prior verifiable parental consent, we will remove his or her personally identifiable information from our files.

The statements above describe the personal information we collect about you, why we collect it, how we use it and when we share it with third parties. Our policy also describes the choices you can make about how we collect and use your information. If you have any questions about our privacy policy, please call us at 800.942.3378 or send e-mail to [mail@lydiasuniforms.com](mailto:mail@lydiasuniforms.com).  You may also write to us at: 

Lydia's Professional Uniforms   
2547 Three Mile Road NW Ste F   
Grand Rapids, MI 49534

If our information practices change in the future, we will let you know by posting the policy changes on our Web site or by communicating directly with you. We will notify you of any such change before we use your information in a manner not previously disclosed in our privacy policy. You will have the opportunity at that time to opt out of any new use of your information.

**SECURITY STATEMENT**   
Protecting the safety of your credit card information is important to us.  We use Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) technology to protect the security of your credit card information as it is transmitted to us.  SSL is the gold standard in Internet encryption technology, which is a fancy way of saying that it's a highly sophisticated method of scrambling data as it travels from your computer to our website's servers.

To make sure you are accessing our secure server before you submit personal financial information, look at the lower left-hand corner of your browser. If you see an unbroken key or a closed lock (depending upon your browser), then SSL is active. To double-check for security, look at the URL or Location line of your browser. If you have accessed a secure server, the first characters of the address in that line should change from "http" to "https."

If you're not quite comfortable shopping online, or would prefer to make your purchase via telephone, just give us a call at 800.942.3378. Our customer service representatives are standing by 24 hours a day, seven days a week. They'll be happy to take your LydiasUniforms.com order right over the phone.

**GENERAL BROWSING   
**LydiasUniforms.com gathers navigational information about where you go on our website. This information allows us to see which areas of LydiasUniforms.com are most visited and helps us better understand our customers' experience at LydiasUniforms.com. This helps us improve the quality of visitors' online shopping experiences by recognizing and delivering more of the features, services and products our visitors prefer. Additional non-personally identifiable information (i.e. domain type, browser version, service provider and IP address) may be collected which will provide information regarding your use of our Web site (such as the time of your last visit to a page on our site).

**COLLECTION, DISCLOSURE, AND USAGE OF PERSONAL INFORMATION   
**We do not provide e-mail addresses to third parties.  However, if you purchase merchandise through LydiasUniforms.com or if you are added to our catalog mailing list, your name and mailing address will be added to the Lydia 's print catalog mailing list and database. Please be aware that we sometimes make our print catalog customer mailing and shipping lists available to companies whose products you may find of interest.

From time to time, we may also send you email to help us learn more about your shopping preferences. In addition, we may use information about your product interests and purchases to help us improve our site design and your shopping experience. If you make a purchase online or over the phone, we may also send you notice about our products, services, and promotions through postal mail.

To serve you better, we may combine information you give us online and in our stores as well as information about your product interests and purchases. In addition, we may combine information you provide with demographic information that is publicly available. We use this combined information to enhance and personalize your shopping experience with us, and to communicate with you by email or postal mail about our products, services, and promotions that may be of interest to you. If you do not want us to use your information as described above, please contact customer service by calling 800.942.3378 or email [mail@lydiasuniforms.com](mailto:mail@lydiasuniforms.com).

**LIST REMOVAL INSTRUCT IONS   
**If you would like your name and email address removed from our email list, please e-mail us at [mail@lydiasuniforms.com](mailto:mail@lydiasuniforms.com).  If you would like to be removed from our catalog mailing list, please send your full name, address as it is printed on the catalog, and catalog keycode to [mail@lydiasuniforms.com](mailto:mail@lydiasuniforms.com).  You may also call 800.942.3378 or write to:

Lydia's Professional Uniforms   
2547 Three Mile Road NW Ste F   
Grand Rapids, MI 49534

Please note that such requests may take up to six to eight weeks to become effective. In addition, if you ask us to remove your name and address from our email or postal mailing lists, we will maintain your name in a "do not mail" file to ensure that we can honor your request. Please also note that when you make a purchase, we will send you email to confirm your order and may also need to contact you via phone, postal mail or email if we have other questions regarding your order.

**USE OF COOKIES**   
A cookie is a small data file that Web sites often store on your computer's hard drive when you visit their sites. A cookie may contain information (such as a unique user ID), that is used to track the pages of the sites you've visited. We use cookies but do not store personally identifiable information in your cookie.

We use cookies in order to improve your shopping experience. When you visit LydiasUniforms.com, your cookie helps us keep track of your order as you shop at our site. If you have saved your information with us, your cookie allows us to recognize you when you return to our site and provides you with access to your account information. If you saved your information with or order from us, we also use cookies to monitor and maintain information about your use of our site. If you have not saved your information with or ordered from us, we may monitor and maintain information about your use of our website in a manner that does not identify you. In either case, this information helps us serve you better by improving our site design, as well as our products, services, contests, and promotions.

We also use cookies to track and maintain the identity of the website you visited immediately prior to ours to further improve our site design and to fulfill contracts with our business partners. We do not otherwise track any information about your use of other websites.

You can refuse cookies by turning them off in your browser. If you turn off cookies, though, we will not be able to track your order or enable you to make a purchase from our site. Nor will we be able to recognize you as a signed up user to allow you access to your account information.

**LINKS   
**For your convenience, our website may contain links to other sites. LydiasUniforms.com is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such Web sites. ****

**What our customers are saying about us:**   

"Very fast service. Good email communication about order confirmation. Product was exactly as advertised."
